export const QuizQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 
        // eslint-disable-next-line max-len
        'If you stand on a rock and throw a rubber duck 8 meters, and then step down and throw the duck again, how far will it go?',
        answerOne: '12 meters, of course',
        answerTwo: 'Depends on the direction of the wind',
        correctAnswer: '8 meters; you haven´t picked it up yet',
        alt: 'black rubber duck with text saying "system failure" and random numbers displayed vertically',
        src: '../assets/images/system-failure-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'The very first rubber ducks were made in late 1800. What couldn´t they do?',
        answerOne: 'Sink',
        answerTwo: 'Be chewed on',
        correctAnswer: 'Float',
        alt: 'rubber duck sitting by a computer',
        src: '../assets/images/programmer-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 
        // eslint-disable-next-line max-len
        'Lizzy the duck was faster than Bob the duck at swimming. Bob was faster than Lizzy at flying. Lizzy was yellower than Bob. What color is Bob?',
        answerOne: 'Red',
        answerTwo: 'Yellow',
        correctAnswer: 'Orange',
        alt: 'cute rubber duck with big eyes, having a red text in front of it, saying "Ready, set, go!"',
        src: '../assets/images/ready-set-go.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'How does a rubber duck spend its weekends?',
        answerOne: 'Ducking responsibilities',
        answerTwo: 'Quacking jokes at a comedy club',
        correctAnswer: 'Taking a relaxing bubble bath',
        alt: 'relaxed rubber duck taking a bubble bath',
        src: '../assets/images/bubble-bath.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Which of the following have rubber ducks been used to measure?',
        answerOne: 'Rubber ducks have been employed to study the migratory patterns of deep-sea creatures.',
        answerTwo: 'Rubber ducks have been utilized to map underwater geological features and topography.',
        correctAnswer: 'Rubber ducks have been used to measure ocean currents.',
        alt: 'rubber duck in clear water with a group of blurry rubber ducks behind it',
        src: '../assets/images/duckrace.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What prestigious award did the esteemed rubber duck receive in 2023 for its outstanding contributions to bath-time entertainment and quacking innovation?',
        answerOne: 'The Nobel Quackson Prize',
        answerTwo: 'The Ducky Distinguished Award',
        correctAnswer: 'The Golden Quacker Prize',
        alt: 'yellow rubber duck with blue eyes, wearing a colorful sombrero',
        src: '../assets/images/sombrero.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'How many duck fits in a bathtub',
        answerOne: 'Maybe 20?',
        answerTwo: '500 sounds reasonable',
        correctAnswer: 'As many as you put in',
        alt: 'lots of rubber ducks in a pile',
        src: '../assets/images/rubberduckies.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What unique feature do many rubber ducks have to ensure safety during playtime?',
        answerOne: 'Anti-slip bottoms for bathtub stability',
        answerTwo: 'Buoyancy control to prevent tipping',
        correctAnswer: 'Non-toxic materials for safe chewing',
        alt: 'rubber duck wearing a red t-shirt that says "Game Over", holding a gamepad',
        src: '../assets/images/game-over.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What material is commonly used to make traditional yellow rubber ducks, ensuring their iconic appearance?',
        answerOne: 'Latex',
        answerTwo: 'Silicone',
        correctAnswer: 'Vinyl',
        alt: 'an ordinary yellow and happy rubber duck',
        src: '../assets/images/happy-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'To meet international safety standards, rubber ducks often undergo testing for which important quality?',
        answerOne: 'Temperature resistance',
        answerTwo: 'Phthalate-free composition',
        correctAnswer: 'Flotation efficiency',
        alt: 'rubber duck wearing a cap that says "bye bye", holding a napkin and has a teardrop from it´s eye',
        src: '../assets/images/sad-duck-bye.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Rubber ducks have been featured in various pop culture references, but in which animated movie did a rubber duck play a memorable role? ',
        answerOne: 'Finding Nemo',
        answerTwo: 'The Little Mermaid',
        correctAnswer: 'Toy Story',
        alt: 'four rubber ducks in swimwear, holding surfboards',
        src: '../assets/images/surfer-ducks.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'In 2001, a giant rubber duck designed by Florentijn Hofman became a global sensation. In which city did it make its first public appearance?',
        answerOne: 'Helsinki',
        answerTwo: 'Tokyo',
        correctAnswer: 'Amsterdam',
        alt: 'one superlarge rubber duck',
        src: '../assets/images/large-duckie.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What term is commonly used to describe the phenomenon of rubber ducks accidentally being released into the ocean, contributing to the study of ocean currents?',
        answerOne: 'Ducky Drift',
        answerTwo: 'Aqua Migration',
        correctAnswer: 'Oceanic Quackflow',
        alt: 'lots of colorful rubber ducks washed up on shore',
        src: '../assets/images/at-the-lake.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What secret society do rubber ducks belong to, dedicated to maintaining order in the bathtub?',
        answerOne: 'Quackers United',
        answerTwo: 'The Rubber Alliance',
        correctAnswer: 'Illumiquacki',
        alt: 'purple rubber duck with hair and a horn like a unicorn',
        src: '../assets/images/unicorn-rubber-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'In the rubber duck Olympics, which event do they take most seriously to showcase their athletic prowess?',
        answerOne: 'Duckling Diving',
        answerTwo: 'Waddle Marathon',
        correctAnswer: 'Synchronized Quacking',
        alt: 'rubber duck dressed in blue cheerleading outfit holding pom-poms',
        src: '../assets/images/blue-cheer-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: 'What is the preferred genre of music among rubber ducks, believed to enhance their quacking abilities?',
        answerOne: 'Jazz Ducktette',
        answerTwo: 'Hip-Hop Quackadelic',
        correctAnswer: 'Classical Quackphony',
        alt: 'rubber duck wearing sunglasses, floating in clear water',
        src: '../assets/images/cool-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: 'Rubber ducks are known for their smooth sailing, but which famous pirate rubber duck led a daring expedition in search of the elusive "Bath-treasure"?',
        answerOne: 'Duckbeard the Plunderer',
        answerTwo: 'Black Beak the Buccaneer',
        correctAnswer: 'Captain Quack Sparrow',
        alt: 'rubber duck in pirate outfit with a hook on the left wing, and holding a sword with the other',
        src: '../assets/images/pirate-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: 'To promote relaxation, some rubber ducks have taken up mindfulness practices. What is their preferred meditation technique? ',
        answerOne: 'Yoga Duckpose',
        answerTwo: 'Tranquil Waddling',
        correctAnswer: 'Zen Quacktation',
        alt: 'clear pool water with a curious-looking rubber duck in the lower right corner',
        src: '../assets/images/pool-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: 'What is the optimal number of rubber ducks needed for a world-class quacking symphony? ',
        answerOne: 'Solo Duckist',
        answerTwo: 'Quacktet',
        correctAnswer: 'Duckharmonic Ensemble',
        alt: 'lots of rubber ducks in rows',
        src: '../assets/images/rows-of-ducks.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: 'During the Rubber Duck Olympics, which event involves ducks navigating a challenging obstacle course in the bathtub?',
        answerOne: 'Aqua Agility Challenge',
        answerTwo: 'Tubstacle Trials',
        correctAnswer: 'Slippery Slide Sprint',
        alt: 'rubber duck dressed in red cheerleading outfit holding pom-poms',
        src: '../assets/images/cheerleader.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: 'Rubber ducks are rumored to have their own version of a Nobel Prize. What is it called?',
        answerOne: 'The Noble Quackson Laureate',
        answerTwo: 'Duckovation Prize',
        correctAnswer: 'Quackademic Excellence Award',
        alt: 'rubber duck holding a star shaped sign saying congratulations, and three balloons',
        src: '../assets/images/congratulations.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: 'What is the preferred method of communication among rubber ducks when organizing a synchronized swimming routine?',
        answerOne: 'Waddle Code',
        answerTwo: 'Floatation Chatter',
        correctAnswer: 'Quackmunication',
        alt: 'four rubber ducks floating in a line',
        src: '../assets/images/ducks-in-line.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: 'Rubber ducks are known for their adventurous spirit. What is their favorite bedtime story genre?',
        answerOne: 'Duckish Fairy Quacks',
        answerTwo: 'Quacktion Adventures',
        correctAnswer: 'Bedtime Quacktales',
        alt: 'an angry-looking rubber duck disguised as batman',
        src: '../assets/images/angry-batman.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: 'In the rubber duck culinary world, what is considered the ultimate comfort food?',
        answerOne: 'Waddlecakes with Syrup',
        answerTwo: 'Duckling Dumplings',
        correctAnswer: 'Quackaroni and Cheese',
        alt: 'rubber duck wearing chef´s outfit holding a cookbook and a covered plate',
        src: '../assets/images/chef-duck.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: 'Rubber ducks are known to participate in fashion shows. What is the latest trend in duck attire?',
        answerOne: 'Quack Couture',
        answerTwo: 'Feathery Fashionista',
        correctAnswer: 'Dapper Duck Ensemble',
        alt: 'rubber ducks in wedding attire',
        src: '../assets/images/wedding-ducks.webp',
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        question: 'What is the secret ingredient in the world-famous rubber duck soup that´s rumored to bring good luck?',
        answerOne: 'Paddle Spice',
        answerTwo: 'Waddle Wonder Herb',
        correctAnswer: 'Quack Essence',
        alt: 'four rubber ducks wearing partyhats and holding gifts',
        src: '../assets/images/party-ducks.webp',
    },
];
